<?xml version="1.0"?>

<resources>

    <string name="app_name">TourGuideApp</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->


    <string name="HistorialPlaces">Historical Places</string>

    <string name="FoodStreets">Food</string>

    <string name="ShoppingPlaces">Shopping Places</string>

    <string name="Hotels">Hotels</string>

    <string name="Specials">Specials</string>
    <string name="ras_mancha">Ras Mancha</string>
    <string name="pancha_ratna_shyam_rai_temple">Pancha Ratna Shyam Rai temple</string>
    <string name="jorebangla_temple">JoreBangla Temple</string>
    <string name="madan_mohan_temple">Madan Mohan Temple</string>
    <string name="radha_shyam_temple">Radha Shyam Temple</string>
    <string name="radhe_shyam_temple">Radhe Shyam Temple</string>
    <string name="lalji_temple">Lalji Temple</string>
    <string name="dalmadal_kaman">DalMadal Kaman</string>
    <string name="mrinmoyee_temple">Mrinmoyee Temple</string>
    <string name="the_rasmancha_bengali_raasmoncho_is_a_historical_temple_located_at_bishnupur_bankura_district_west_bengal_india_it_was_commissioned_by_mallabhum_king_hambir_malla_dev_bir_hambir_in_1600_ce_length_and_breadth_of_this_temple_is_24_5_meter_and_the_height_is_12_5_meter_the_base_or_altar_of_the_temple_is_made_of_laterite_stone_and_upper_part_is_made_with_bricks_upper_structure_looks_like_a_pyramid_middle_part_resembles_bengali_huts_and_the_arches_of_the_lower_part_resembles_islamic_architecture_during_the_vaishnava_ras_festival_all_the_radha_krishna_idols_of_bishnupur_town_used_to_be_brought_here_to_be_worshipped_by_the_citizens_the_annual_festival_was_held_till_1932">The Rasmancha (Bengali: রাসমঞ্চ; Raasmoncho) is a historical temple located at Bishnupur, Bankura district, West Bengal, India. It was commissioned by Mallabhum king Hambir Malla Dev (Bir Hambir) in 1600 CE. Length and breadth of this temple is 24.5 meter and the height is 12.5 meter. The base or altar of the temple is made of laterite stone and upper part is made with bricks. Upper structure looks like a pyramid. Middle part resembles Bengali huts and the arches of the lower part resembles Islamic architecture. During the Vaishnava Ras festival, all the Radha Krishna idols of Bishnupur town used to be brought here to be worshipped by the citizens. The annual festival was held till 1932.</string>
    <string name="another_ancient_temple_in_bishnupur_manipur_is_jorebangla_temple_it_was_malla_king_raghunath_singha_dev_who_built_this_beautiful_hindu_temple_in_the_year_1655_the_temple_is_also_known_as_yorubangala_and_boasts_a_magnificent_architectural_design_however_the_structure_of_the_temple_is_seated_on_a_high_platform_using_laterite_bricks_although_the_temple_is_not_much_into_the_spotlight_in_the_outer_world_but_it_is_very_much_popular_in_the_region_throughout_the_year_this_popular_tourist_attraction_in_bishnupur_is_explored_by_numerous_travellers_who_know_about_this_place_one_of_the_highlights_of_this_17th_century_temple_is_the_intricate_carvings_that_are_put_up_on_both_outer_and_inner_walls_of_the_temple_on_a_trip_to_bishnupur_jorebangla_temple_is_an_important_attraction_to_visit">Another ancient temple in Bishnupur, Manipur is Jorebangla Temple. It was Malla King, Raghunath Singha Dev who built this beautiful Hindu temple in the year 1655. The temple is also known as Yorubangala and boasts a magnificent architectural design. However, the structure of the temple is seated on a high platform using Laterite bricks. Although the temple is not much into the spotlight in the outer world, but, it is very much popular in the region. Throughout the year, this popular tourist attraction in Bishnupur is explored by numerous travellers who know about this place. One of the highlights of this 17th-century temple is the intricate carvings that are put up on both outer and inner walls of the temple. On a trip to Bishnupur, Jorebangla Temple is an important attraction to visit.</string>
    <string name="built_by_king_raghunath_singha_it_stands_on_a_low_square_plinth_and_consists_of_an_ambulatory_pathway_with_a_porch_opened_by_three_arches_on_the_four_sides_of_the_temple_the_central_shikhara_is_octagonal_while_the_rest_four_are_square_the_walls_are_richly_decorated_with_terracotta_carvings_featuring_aspects_of_lord_krishna_s_life">Built by King Raghunath Singha. It stands on a low square plinth and consists of an ambulatory pathway with a porch opened by three arches on the four sides of the temple. The central shikhara is octagonal, while the rest four are square. The walls are richly decorated with terracotta carvings featuring aspects of Lord Krishna’s life.</string>
    <string name="traces_its_history_from_1758_radha_shyam_temple_in_bishnupur_was_constructed_by_the_king_chaitanya_singha_devoted_to_lord_krishna_the_temple_is_located_near_another_historical_shrine_jorbangla_temple_radha_shyam_temple_is_dome_shaped_and_it_lies_within_an_enclosure_which_is_surrounded_by_the_boundary_wall_along_with_its_high_sacred_significance_the_temple_is_known_for_its_aesthetic_architecture_which_makes_a_popular_tourist_attraction_in_bishnupur_because_of_its_historical_significance_and_heritage_value_the_temple_is_well_preserved_by_the_archaeological_survey_of_india_asi_enshrining_the_images_of_lord_krishna_and_radha_in_the_sanctum_the_radha_shyam_temple_is_esteemed_as_the_living_shrine_in_the_region_along_with_the_radha_and_shyam_lord_krishna_the_sanctum_also_includes_the_images_of_nityananda_and_chaitanya_in_the_temple_vicinity_there_is_another_shrine_which_houses_the_idols_of_lord_jagannath_of_puri_and_also_nityananda_and_chaitanya_throughout_the_year_this_beautiful_temple_in_bishnupur_is_visited_by_numerous_visitors_some_come_to_offer_their_homage_while_others_visit_the_temple_just_to_adore_exquisite_grandeur">Traces its history from 1758, Radha Shyam Temple in Bishnupur was constructed by the King Chaitanya Singha. Devoted to Lord Krishna, the temple is located near another historical shrine Jorbangla Temple. Radha Shyam Temple is dome-shaped and it lies within an enclosure which is surrounded by the boundary wall. Along with its high sacred significance, the temple is known for its aesthetic architecture which makes a popular tourist attraction in Bishnupur. Because of its historical significance and heritage value, the temple is well preserved by the Archaeological Survey of India (ASI). Enshrining the images of Lord Krishna and Radha in the sanctum, the Radha Shyam Temple is esteemed as the living shrine in the region. Along with the Radha and Shyam (Lord Krishna), the sanctum also includes the images of Nityananda and Chaitanya. In the temple vicinity, there is another shrine which houses the idols of Lord Jagannath of Puri and also Nityananda and Chaitanya. Throughout the year, this beautiful temple in Bishnupur is visited by numerous visitors; some come to offer their homage, while, others visit the temple just to adore exquisite grandeur.</string>
    <string name="lalji_temple_has_been_built_by_malla_king_bir_singha_with_shikhara_and_built_on_raised_platform_of_square_shape_this_temple_has_been_devoted_to_radha_krishna_and_is_similar_to_that_of_bengali_architecture_with_ornamental_stucco_decorations_in_front_of_the_temple_there_is_dancing_hall_and_there_is_tower_in_the_west_dedicated_to_raghunath_outer_yard_is_divided_from_the_inner_by_a_wall_and_contains_a_small_pancharatna_temple_of_kameswar_siva_the_temple_is_enclosed_by_wall_entirely_with_a_gateway_passage_towards_east_in_front_of_the_gateway_are_two_cars_are_there_one_for_lord_lalji_and_the_other_from_lord_raghunath_they_are_taken_out_in_procession_during_dussera_festival_there_are_inscriptions_in_bengali_at_several_places_trains_and_buses_both_can_be_taken_depending_on_the_comfort_of_person">Lalji Temple has been built by Malla king Bir Singha, with Shikhara and built on raised platform of square shape. This temple has been devoted to Radha-Krishna and is similar to that of Bengali architecture with ornamental stucco decorations. In front of the temple there is dancing hall and there is tower in the west dedicated to Raghunath. Outer yard is divided from the inner by a wall, and contains a small Pancharatna temple of Kameswar Siva. The temple is enclosed by wall entirely with a gateway passage towards east. In front of the gateway are two cars are there one for Lord Lalji and the other from lord Raghunath. They are taken out in procession during Dussera festival. There are inscriptions in Bengali at several places. Trains and buses both can be taken depending on the comfort of person.</string>
    <string name="during_the_reign_of_bir_hambir_the_dal_madal_one_of_the_largest_bored_cannons_even_made_was_founded_demonstrating_the_skill_of_artisans_of_that_time_dal_madal_was_made_by_jagannath_karmakar_dal_madal_means_destruction_of_enemy">During the reign of Bir Hambir the Dal Madal, one of the largest-bored cannons even made, was founded, demonstrating the skill of artisans of that time. Dal Madal was made by Jagannath Karmakar. Dal Madal means destruction of enemy.</string>
    <string name="mrinmoyee_temple_is_dedicated_to_goddess_durga_and_is_situated_in_bishnupur_at_bankura_district_it_is_a_very_old_temple_and_is_rich_in_heritage_durga_puja_which_is_observed_every_year_in_this_temple_is_over_1000_years_old_it_is_unbelievable_but_true_it_gets_this_name_because_of_the_fact_that_the_malla_dynasty_used_to_rule_then_and_it_was_under_their_governance_that_this_temple_came_up_it_is_the_oldest_durga_puja_in_bengal_and_it_still_beholds_its_rich_culture_in_an_undiluted_way_history_of_the_mrinmoyee_temple_raghunath_was_crowned_as_the_first_king_of_malla_dynasty_at_pradamnapur_king_jagat_malla_shifted_his_capital_from_pradamnapur_to_bishnupur_because_of_the_latter_s_better_positioning_with_respect_to_safety_bishnupur_is_mostly_famous_for_its_terracotta_tradition_but_it_also_proudly_is_the_place_where_the_oldest_durga_puja_of_the_state_happens_king_jagat_malla_established_the_mrinmoyee_temple_in_997_ad_actually_jagat_malla_was_ordered_by_maa_mrinmoyee_to_build_this_temple_in_his_dreams_the_idol_is_made_of_ganga_clay_the_57th_generation_of_the_malla_dynasty_is_there_at_present">Mrinmoyee Temple is dedicated to Goddess Durga and is situated in Bishnupur at Bankura district. It is a very old temple and is rich in heritage. Durga Puja which is observed every year in this temple is over 1000 years old. It is unbelievable, but true. It gets this name because of the fact that the Malla dynasty used to rule then and it was under their governance that this temple came up. It is the oldest Durga Puja in Bengal and it still beholds its rich culture, in an undiluted way. History of the Mrinmoyee temple - Raghunath was crowned as the first king of Malla dynasty at Pradamnapur. King Jagat Malla shifted his capital from Pradamnapur to Bishnupur because of the latter’s better positioning with respect to safety. Bishnupur is mostly famous for its terracotta tradition, but it also proudly is the place where the oldest Durga Puja of the state happens. King Jagat Malla established the Mrinmoyee temple in 997 AD. Actually, Jagat Malla was ordered by Maa Mrinmoyee to build this temple, in his dreams. The idol is made of Ganga clay. The 57th generation of the Malla dynasty is there at present.</string>
    <string name="mohua">Mohua</string>
    <string name="chicken_pakoras_from_bishnupur_street_food">Chicken Pakoras, from Bishnupur Street Food</string>
    <string name="meethi_lassi_from_jeda_lassi_pokabandh_bazaar">Meethi Lassi from Jeda Lassi, Pokabandh Bazaar</string>
    <string name="momo_from_sana_momo_centre_shalbagan_mayra_pukur">Momo, from Sana Momo Centre, Shalbagan, Mayra Pukur</string>
    <string name="lassi_from_lassi_centre_and_resturant_poka_bandh_north_chawk_bazar">Lassi, from Lassi Centre and Resturant, Poka Bandh North, Chawk Bazar</string>
    <string name="biryani_from_heritage_no1_biryani_and_haji_biryani_house_dalmadal_para">Biryani, from Heritage No1 Biryani and Haji Biryani House, Dalmadal Para</string>
    <string name="postor_bora_from_park_hotel_and_resturant_high_school_more_dalmadal_para">Postor Bora, from Park Hotel and Resturant, High School more, Dalmadal Para</string>
    <string name="pera_from_kalpataru_mistanna_bhandar_kalindibandh">Pera, from Kalpataru Mistanna Bhandar, Kalindibandh</string>
    <string name="mecha_sandesh_from_maa_chinnamasta_mistanna_vandar_bishnupur_college_rd_dalmadal_para">Mecha Sandesh, from Maa Chinnamasta Mistanna Vandar, Bishnupur College Rd, Dalmadal Para</string>
    <string name="when_it_comes_to_sweet_delicacies_none_can_beat_bengalis_however_in_the_recent_past_with_introduction_of_many_north_indian_sweets_on_the_bengali_platter_many_of_our_indigenous_sweets_are_missing_and_some_are_on_way_of_extinction_this_is_primarily_because_many_sweet_makers_do_not_even_know_what_their_ancestors_made_and_many_recipes_are_not_shared_down_generations">When it comes to sweet delicacies, none can beat Bengalis. However, in the recent past with introduction of many North Indian sweets on the Bengali platter, many of our indigenous sweets are missing and some are on way of extinction. This is primarily because many sweet makers do not even know what their ancestors made and many recipes are not shared down generations.</string>
    <string name="peda_pronounced_pe_a_or_pera_is_a_sweet_dish_hailing_from_the_indian_subcontinent_it_originated_from_mathura_uttar_pradesh_india_usually_prepared_in_thick_semi_soft_pieces_its_main_ingredients_are_khoa_sugar_and_traditional_flavorings_including_cardamom_seeds_pistachio_nuts_and_saffron_its_colour_varies_from_a_creamy_white_to_a_caramel_colour_the_word_peda_is_also_generically_used_to_mean_a_sphere_of_any_doughy_substance_such_as_flour_or_khoa_variant_spellings_and_names_for_the_dessert_include_pedha_penda_in_gujarati_and_pera_pedas_originated_in_the_city_of_mathura_in_the_present_day_uttar_pradesh_the_mathura_peda_is_the_characteristic_variety_from_the_city_from_uttar_pradesh_the_peda_spread_to_many_parts_of_the_indian_subcontinent_thakur_ram_ratan_singh_of_lucknow_who_migrated_to_dharwad_in_the_present_day_karnataka_in_the_1850s_introduced_pedas_there_this_distinct_variety_is_now_famous_as_the_dharwad_pedha_kandi_peda_from_satara_in_maharashtra_is_another_variety_of_peda_dood_peda_made_famous_by_the_nandini_milk_co_operative_in_karnataka_is_another_popular_variety_as_with_laddoos_pedas_are_sometimes_used_as_prasadam_in_religious_services">Peda (pronounced [ˈpeːɽa]) or Pera is a sweet dish hailing from the Indian subcontinent. It originated from Mathura, Uttar Pradesh, India. Usually prepared in thick, semi-soft pieces, its main ingredients are khoa, sugar and traditional flavorings including cardamom seeds, pistachio nuts and saffron. Its colour varies from a creamy white to a caramel colour. The word peda is also generically used to mean a sphere of any doughy substance such as flour or khoa. Variant spellings and names for the dessert include pedha, penda (in Gujarati) and pera. Pedas originated in the city of Mathura in the present-day Uttar Pradesh. The Mathura Peda is the characteristic variety from the city. From Uttar Pradesh, the peda spread to many parts of the Indian subcontinent. Thakur Ram Ratan Singh of Lucknow who migrated to Dharwad (in the present-day Karnataka) in the 1850s introduced pedas there. This distinct variety is now famous as the Dharwad pedha. Kandi Peda from Satara in Maharashtra is another variety of peda. Dood peda, made famous by the Nandini Milk Co-operative in Karnataka, is another popular variety. As with laddoos, pedas are sometimes used as prasadam in religious services.</string>
    <string name="postor_bora_is_an_exemplary_traditional_bengali_food_which_is_known_for_its_extraordinary_flavour_and_texture_it_is_hugely_popular_among_bongs_in_west_bengal_it_is_the_amalgamation_of_poppy_seeds_paste_grated_coconut_onions_green_chillies_and_rice_flour_which_are_shallow_fried_as_fritters_in_mustard_oil_it_is_a_perfect_fritter_with_the_outer_crisp_containing_poppy_seeds_toping_and_is_tender_at_the_centre_it_is_mostly_served_as_a_starter_or_as_a_side_with_main_course_to_relish">Postor Bora is an exemplary traditional Bengali food which is known for its extraordinary flavour and texture. It is hugely popular among Bongs in West Bengal. It is the amalgamation of poppy seeds paste, grated coconut, onions, green chillies and rice flour which are shallow fried as fritters in mustard oil. It is a perfect fritter with the outer crisp containing poppy seeds toping and is tender at the centre. It is mostly served as a starter or as a side with main course to relish.</string>
    <string name="biryani_b_r_j_ni_is_a_mixed_rice_dish_originating_among_the_muslims_of_the_indian_subcontinent_it_is_made_with_indian_spices_rice_and_meat_usually_that_of_chicken_goat_lamb_prawn_fish_and_sometimes_in_addition_eggs_or_vegetables_such_as_potatoes_in_certain_regional_varieties_biryani_is_popular_throughout_the_indian_subcontinent_as_well_as_among_the_diaspora_from_the_region_it_has_gained_popularity_in_south_india_especially_in_tamil_nadu_andhra_pradesh_and_telangana_it_is_also_prepared_in_other_regions_such_as_iraqi_kurdistan">Biryani (/bɪrˈjɑːni/) is a mixed rice dish originating among the Muslims of the Indian subcontinent.It is made with Indian spices, rice, and meat usually that of chicken, goat, lamb, prawn, fish, and sometimes, in addition, eggs or vegetables such as potatoes in certain regional varieties. Biryani is popular throughout the Indian subcontinent, as well as among the diaspora from the region. It has gained popularity in South India especially in Tamil Nadu, Andhra Pradesh and Telangana. It is also prepared in other regions such as Iraqi Kurdistan.</string>
    <string name="chicken_pakora_or_chicken_pakoda_recipe_is_an_amazing_chicken_fritter_recipe_using_boneless_chicken_maida_and_spices_there_are_several_other_chicken_starters_on_my_blog_such_as_tandoori_chicken_these_pakoras_are_an_absolute_delight_to_have_as_evening_tea_time_snacks">Chicken Pakora or chicken pakoda recipe is an amazing chicken fritter recipe using boneless chicken, maida and spices. There are several other chicken starters on my blog such as tandoori chicken. These pakoras are an absolute delight to have as evening tea-time snacks.</string>
    <string name="momo_tibetan_wylie_mog_mog_is_a_type_of_tibetan_dumpling_dish_it_is_popular_in_tibet_nepal_india_and_in_the_regions_straddling_the_himalayas_between_south_asia_and_east_asia_momo_is_found_in_the_cuisines_of_nepal_tibet_it_is_similar_to_baozi_jiaozi_and_mantou_in_chinese_cuisine_buuz_in_mongolian_cuisine_gyoza_in_japanese_cuisine_mandu_in_korean_cuisine_and_manti_in_turkic_cuisines_albeit_heavily_influenced_by_the_cuisine_of_the_indian_subcontinent_with_indian_spices_and_herbs_momo_is_extremely_popular_in_south_asia_and_can_be_found_in_every_kind_of_shop_from_restaurants_to_street_vendors"><![CDATA[Momo (Tibetan: མོག་མོག་, Wylie: mog mog) is a type of Tibetan dumpling dish. It is popular in Tibet, Nepal, India and in the regions straddling the Himalayas between South Asia and East Asia.Momo is found in the cuisines of Nepal & Tibet. It is similar to baozi, jiaozi and mantou in Chinese cuisine, buuz in Mongolian cuisine, gyoza in Japanese cuisine, mandu in Korean cuisine and manti in Turkic cuisines, albeit heavily influenced by the cuisine of the Indian subcontinent with Indian spices and herbs. Momo is extremely popular in South Asia and can be found in every kind of shop from restaurants to street vendors.]]></string>
    <string name="hotel_raj_and_restaurant">Hotel Raj and Restaurant</string>
    <string name="park_hotel_and_restaurant">Park Hotel And Restaurant</string>
    <string name="hotel_sneha">Hotel Sneha</string>
    <string name="hotel_laxmi_park">Hotel Laxmi Park</string>
    <string name="sree_hotel_and_restaurant">Sree Hotel And Restaurant</string>
    <string name="shibkali_lodge">Shibkali Lodge</string>
    <string name="swapnil_hotel_and_restaurant">Swapnil Hotel And Restaurant</string>
    <string name="monalisa_hotel_and_restaurant">Monalisa Hotel And Restaurant</string>
    <string name="at_monalisa_hotel_and_restaurant_the_recipe_of_nicely_cooked_fish_is_a_story_that_ends_up_with_a_really_good_meal_the_convenient_location_of_this_place_makes_it_easy_to_reach_by_any_transport_the_accommodating_staff_works_hard_stays_positive_and_makes_this_place_wonderful_service_at_this_spot_is_something_one_can_name_fast_from_the_visitors_point_of_view_prices_are_reasonable_the_comfortable_atmosphere_is_what_monalisa_hotel_and_restaurant_is_about_but_this_place_hasn_t_earned_a_high_rating_from_google_users">At Monalisa Hotel And Restaurant, the recipe of nicely cooked fish is a story that ends up with a really good meal. The convenient location of this place makes it easy to reach by any transport. The accommodating staff works hard, stays positive and makes this place wonderful. Service at this spot is something one can name fast. From the visitors\' point of view, prices are reasonable. The comfortable atmosphere is what Monalisa Hotel And Restaurant is about. But this place hasn\'t earned a high rating from Google users.</string>
    <string name="the_service_is_always_fast_take_it_into_account_but_swapnil_hotel_restaurant_has_been_rated_below_average_by_google"><![CDATA[The service is always fast, take it into account. But Swapnil Hotel & Restaurant has been rated below average by Google.]]></string>
    <string name="shib_kali_lodge_in_bishnupur_has_a_restaurant_and_a_shared_lounge_all_rooms_boast_a_kitchen_a_flat_screen_tv_with_cable_channels_and_a_private_bathroom_the_accommodation_features_a_24_hour_front_desk_a_shared_kitchen_and_luggage_storage_for_guests_the_rooms_at_the_hotel_are_fitted_with_a_seating_area_an_american_breakfast_is_available_each_morning_at_shibkali_lodge_we_speak_your_language">Shib Kali Lodge in Bishnupur has a restaurant and a shared lounge. All rooms boast a kitchen, a flat-screen TV with cable channels, and a private bathroom. The accommodation features a 24-hour front desk, a shared kitchen and luggage storage for guests.The rooms at the hotel are fitted with a seating area.An American breakfast is available each morning at Shibkali Lodge.We speak your language!</string>
    <string name="if_you_never_happened_to_try_vegetarian_cuisine_get_your_chance_at_this_restaurant_sree_hotel_restaurant_is_remarkable_for_its_fast_service_from_the_guests_viewpoint_prices_are_good_but_google_users_haven_t_given_this_place_a_high_rating_lunch_dinner_rice_biryani"><![CDATA[If you never happened to try Vegetarian cuisine, get your chance at this restaurant. Sree Hotel & Restaurant is remarkable for its fast service. From the guests\' viewpoint, prices are good. But google users haven\'t given this place a high rating. ->lunch ->dinner ->rice ->biryani]]></string>
    <string name="hotel_laxmi_park_is_a_well_facilitated_hotel_in_bishnupur_in_the_bankura_district_of_west_bengal_the_rooms_in_the_hotel_are_spacious_and_adequately_furnished_with_modern_amenities_famous_attraction_like_bishnupur_museum_1_km_dalmadal_kaman_canon_1_3_km_shyamrai_temple_1_5_km_jorebangla_temple_1_7_km_and_many_more_places_are_at_an_accessible_distance_from_the_property_this_property_is_located_2_2_km_from_bishnupur_railway_station">Hotel Laxmi Park is a well-facilitated hotel in Bishnupur in the Bankura district of West Bengal. The rooms in the hotel are spacious and adequately furnished with modern amenities. Famous attraction like Bishnupur Museum 1 km, Dalmadal Kaman Canon 1.3 km, Shyamrai Temple 1.5 km, Jorebangla Temple 1.7 km and many more places are at an accessible distance from the property. This property is located 2.2 km from Bishnupur Railway Station.</string>
    <string name="rice_chicken_poultry_soup_biryani_borsch_raita_cheese_chicken_and_rice_chilli_chicken_meat_chicken_roti_ice_cream_flija_idli_fish_fried_chicken_lunch_lunchtakeaway_great_service_food_delivery_great_location_breakfast_dinner_friendly_staff_anniversary_outdoor_seating"><![CDATA[-->> rice -->> chicken -->> poultry -->> soup -->> biryani -->> borsch -->> raita -->> cheese -->> chicken and rice -->> chilli chicken -->> meat ->> chicken roti -->> ice cream -->> flija -->> idli -->> fish -->> fried chicken
    2--->>>>      --->>> lunch --->>> lunchtakeaway --->>> great service --->>> food delivery --->>> great location --->>> breakfast --->>> dinner --->>> friendly staff --->>> anniversary --->>> outdoor seating]]></string>
    <string name="hotel_annapurna">Hotel Annapurna</string>
    <string name="if_you_have_never_come_across_indian_cuisine_you_should_reserve_a_table_at_this_restaurant_you_can_have_perfectly_cooked_chicken_and_tasty_roti_at_hotel_raj_restaurant_but_most_visitors_who_use_google_didn_t_give_this_place_a_high_rating"><![CDATA[If you have never come across Indian cuisine, you should reserve a table at this restaurant. You can have perfectly cooked chicken and tasty roti at HOTEL RAJ & RESTAURANT. But most visitors who use Google didn\'t give this place a high rating.]]></string>
    <string name="hotel_annapurna_is_situated_in_the_historic_town_of_bishnupur_of_bankura_district_the_hotel_is_located_at_about_3kms_from_bishnupur_railway_station_and_is_in_close_proximity_to_rashmancha_the_hotel_is_also_well_connected_by_roads_from_bankura_durgapur_asansol_burdwan_and_kolkata_the_hotel_opened_its_doors_for_guests_from_late_2018_welcoming_guests_not_only_from_bengal_but_from_all_across_the_world_this_is_the_only_star_category_hotel_in_and_around_bishnupur_and_is_poised_to_make_one_s_trip_to_bishnupur_more_memorable">Hotel Annapurna is situated in the historic town of Bishnupur of Bankura district. The hotel is located at about 3kms from Bishnupur Railway Station and is in close proximity to Rashmancha. The hotel is also well connected by roads from Bankura, Durgapur, Asansol, Burdwan and Kolkata. The hotel opened its doors for guests from late 2018 welcoming guests not only from Bengal but from all across the world. This is the only star category hotel in and around Bishnupur and is poised to make one’s trip to Bishnupur more memorable.</string>
    <string name="jd_bazaar">Jd Bazaar</string>
    <string name="kolkata_trends">Kolkata Trends</string>
    <string name="chandan_dress_house">Chandan Dress House</string>
    <string name="kaniska">Kaniska</string>
    <string name="anuvab">Anuvab</string>
    <string name="anuska">Anuska</string>
    <string name="m_s_fatelal_oswal">M/S Fatelal Oswal</string>
    <string name="new_anuvab">New Anuvab</string>
    <string name="mallabhum_silk_centre">Mallabhum Silk Centre</string>
    <string name="mens_wear_ladies_wear_kids_wear_fashion_accessories_jewelry_t_shirt_shirt_jeans_trousers_cotton_pant_baba_suit_kurtis_tops_lowers_suits_sarees_bed_sheets_under_garments_lungi_vests_briefs_shoes_sun_glass_goggles_belts_salwar_suits_suit_piece_bags_hand_bags_school_bags_travel_bags_pajama_hosiery_goods_summer_wear_winter_wear_hanky_handkerchief_kurta_pajama_punjabi_ethnic_wear_sports_wear_suitings_shirtings_infant_needs">mens wear, ladies wear, kids wear, fashion accessories, jewelry, t shirt, shirt, jeans, trousers, cotton pant, baba suit, Kurtis, tops, lowers, suits, sarees, bed-sheets, under garments, lungi, vests, briefs, shoes, sun glass, goggles, belts, salwar suits, suit piece, bags, hand bags, school bags, travel bags, pajama, hosiery goods, summer wear, winter wear, hanky, handkerchief, kurta, pajama, punjabi, ethnic wear, sports wear, suitings, shirtings, infant needs</string>
    <string name="kolkata_trends_is_one_of_the_pioneers_in_value_for_money_retail_format_in_west_bengal_and_eastern_india_we_cater_to_modern_lifestyle_by_making_a_wide_portfolio_of_products_available_to_our_customers_at_an_affordable_price">Kolkata Trends is one of the pioneers in Value for Money Retail Format in West Bengal and Eastern India. We cater to modern lifestyle by making a wide portfolio of products available to our customers at an affordable price.</string>
    <string name="chandan_dress_house_has_its_place_in_the_lineup_of_clothing_and_shoes_this_company_has_an_average_score_of_3_by_nicelocal_visitors_and_is_located_by_the_following_address_bishnupur_station_road_bishnupur_bankura_722122">Chandan Dress House has its place in the lineup of Clothing and shoes. This company has an average score of 3 by NiceLocal visitors and is located by the following address: Bishnupur, Station Road, Bishnupur Bankura — 722122.</string>
    <string name="kaniska_is_one_of_the_oldest_and_reputed_garment_shop_of_bishnupur_in_bakura_district_of_west_bengal_in_india_bishnupur_is_known_to_the_world_for_it_s_handmade_products_it_is_famous_for_its_terracotta_temples_malla_shree_krishna_raslilla_and_the_baluchari_sarees_kaniska_is_situated_in_the_bishnupur_center_at_lalbandh_near_pamananda_collage_the_shop_is_one_of_the_oldest_shops_selling_baluchari_sareers_swarnachari_sarees_all_handmade_established_in_the_year_2003_all_sareers_are_manufacted_in_bishnupur_which_are_hand_stictched_the_tradition_of_creating_handmade_sareers_baluchari_and_swarnachari_are_being_done_since_last_50_60_years">Kaniska is one of the oldest and reputed garment shop of Bishnupur in Bakura District of West Bengal in India. Bishnupur is known to the world for it\'s handmade products. It is famous for its terracotta temples Malla Shree Krishna Raslilla and the baluchari sarees. Kaniska is situated in the Bishnupur Center at Lalbandh, Near Pamananda Collage . The shop is one of the oldest shops selling Baluchari Sareers, Swarnachari Sarees all handmade. Established in the year 2003 all sareers are manufacted in Bishnupur which are Hand stictched. The tradition of creating handmade sareers (Baluchari and Swarnachari) are being done since last 50-60 years.</string>
    <string name="_1_what_are_the_various_mode_of_payment_accepted_here_you_can_make_payment_via_cash_2_which_is_the_nearest_landmark_you_can_easily_locate_the_establishment_as_it_is_in_close_proximity_to_boltala_bishnupur_3_what_are_its_hours_of_operation_the_establishment_is_functional_on_monday_9_00_am_9_00_pm_tuesday_9_00_am_9_00_pm_wednesday_9_00_am_9_00_pm_thursday_9_00_am_9_00_pm_friday_9_00_am_9_00_pm_saturday_9_00_am_9_00_pm_sunday_9_00_am_9_00_pm">1. What are the various mode of payment accepted here ? You can make payment Via Cash. 2. Which is the nearest landmark ? You can easily locate the establishment as it is in close proximity to Boltala, Bishnupur 3. What are its hours of operation ? The establishment is functional on Monday:- 9:00 Am - 9:00 Pm Tuesday:- 9:00 Am - 9:00 Pm Wednesday:- 9:00 Am - 9:00 Pm Thursday:- 9:00 Am - 9:00 Pm Friday:- 9:00 Am - 9:00 Pm Saturday:- 9:00 Am - 9:00 Pm Sunday:- 9:00 Am - 9:00 Pm</string>
    <string name="at_anuska_we_are_focused_on_providing_best_collection_of_sarees_with_the_highest_levels_of_customer_satisfaction_we_will_do_everything_we_can_to_meet_your_expectations_with_a_variety_of_offerings_to_choose_from_we_re_sure_you_ll_be_happy_shopping_with_us_visit_our_store_for_beautiful_baluchuri_sarees_banarasi_sarees_kantha_stitch_sarees_swarnachuri_sarees_and_many_more_also_feel_free_to_contact_us_through_our_website">At Anuska, we are focused on providing best collection of Sarees with the highest levels of customer satisfaction – we will do everything we can to meet your expectations.With a variety of offerings to choose from, we’re sure you’ll be happy shopping with us. Visit our store for Beautiful Baluchuri Sarees, Banarasi Sarees, Kantha Stitch Sarees, Swarnachuri Sarees and many more. Also feel free to contact us through our website.</string>
    <string name="m_s_fatelal_oswal_wholesaler_of_bishnupur_3d_pure_silk_pure_dupion_silk_sarees_soft_art_silk_saree_in_bishnupur_bankura_district_west_bengal"><![CDATA[M/s Fatelal Oswal - Wholesaler of bishnupur 3d pure silk, pure dupion silk sarees & soft art silk saree in Bishnupur Bankura District, West Bengal.]]></string>
    <string name="quality_is_our_motto_manufacturer_of_baluchuri_and_swarnachuri_silk_sares">Quality is our Motto(Manufacturer of Baluchuri and Swarnachuri silk sares).</string>
    <string name="silk_sari_baluchari_sari_shop_silk_sari_baluchari_sari_shop_in_bishnupur_baluchari_sari">Silk Sari,Baluchari Sari Shop\tSilk Sari,Baluchari Sari Shop In Bishnupur Baluchari Sari</string>
    <string name="lassi_pronounced_l_s_i_is_a_popular_traditional_dahi_yogurt_based_drink_that_originated_in_the_punjab_region_lassi_is_a_blend_of_yogurt_water_spices_and_sometimes_fruit_namkeen_salty_lassi_is_similar_to_doogh_while_sweet_and_mango_lassis_are_like_milkshakes_lassi_may_be_infused_with_cannabis_in_the_form_of_bhang">Lassi (pronounced [ləsːiː]) is a popular traditional dahi (yogurt)-based drink that originated in the Punjab region. Lassi is a blend of yogurt, water, spices and sometimes fruit. Namkeen (salty) lassi is similar to doogh, while sweet and mango lassis are like milkshakes. Lassi may be infused with cannabis in the form of bhang.</string>
    <string name="tour_guide_app">Tour Guide App</string>
    <string name="madanmohan_temple_was_built_by_malla_king_durjan_singha_pronunciation_sing_ho_in_1695_ad_it_is_relatively_a_bigger_eka_ratna_temple_compared_to_other_similar_temples_in_bishnupur_and_is_important_too_the_temple_has_a_square_base_of_12_2m_x_12_2m_and_a_height_of_10_7m_above_a_moderate_platform_the_roof_of_the_temple_is_typical_bengali_chala_type_surmounted_by_a_single_sikhara_or_tower_the_temple_is_mainly_built_of_earthen_bricks_on_a_laterite_block_platform_and_the_frontal_facade_of_the_temple_is_profusely_decorated_with_rich_terracotta_plaques_depicting_mythological_stories_like_krishna_leela_around_the_innermost_sanctuary_where_the_idol_is_kept_there_are_covered_porches_on_three_sides_except_the_rear_wall_on_each_of_these_three_sides_there_are_three_arched_openings_the_main_entrance_being_on_the_west_for_more_detail_please_see_asi_notice_madanmohan_temple_is_probably_the_most_famous_because_of_the_interesting_story_involving_its_deity_the_original_deity_was_installed_in_a_village_in_bengal_the_fame_of_the_deity_spread_far_and_wide_after_the_personal_visit_by_chaitanya_mahaprabhu_the_famous_vaishnava_saint_so_the_malla_king_carried_the_idol_to_his_capital_at_vana_vishnupur_and_installed_him_in_a_terracotta_temple_built_for_that_purpose_legend_says_that_the_deity_madanmohan_himself_defended_the_malla_king_in_the_battle_with_the_bargi_or_maratha_invaders_who_attacked_bengal_in_1820_the_original_temple_was_destructed_due_to_a_massive_earthquake_after_that_the_present_temple_was_built">Madanmohan temple was built by Malla king Durjan Singha (pronunciation: sing-ho) in 1695 AD. It is relatively a bigger Eka-Ratna temple compared to other similar temples in Bishnupur and is important too. The temple has a square base of 12.2m X 12.2m and a height of 10.7m above a moderate platform. The roof of the temple is typical Bengali \'chala\' type surmounted by a single \'sikhara\' or tower. The temple is mainly built of earthen bricks on a laterite block platform and the frontal facade of the temple is profusely decorated with rich terracotta plaques depicting mythological stories like ‘Krishna Leela’. Around the innermost sanctuary where the idol is kept, there are covered porches on three sides. Except the rear wall, on each of these three sides there are three arched openings, the main entrance being on the west. For more detail please see ASI notice. Madanmohan temple is probably the most famous because of the interesting story involving its deity. The original deity was installed in a village in Bengal. The fame of the deity spread far and wide after the personal visit by Chaitanya Mahaprabhu, the famous Vaishnava saint. So the Malla king carried the idol to his capital at Vana-Vishnupur and installed him in a terracotta temple built for that purpose. Legend says that the deity Madanmohan himself defended the Malla king in the battle with the \'bargi\' or Maratha invaders who attacked Bengal. In 1820, the original temple was destructed due to a massive earthquake. After that the present temple was built.</string>

</resources>